bolmol.com 2015-08-10

# Privacy Policy | Tap It Systems

At Tap It Systems, we respect your personal information as well as our own, and take seriously our privacy obligations. This website describes Tap It Systems approach to privacy for Tap It Systems website(s) and mobile applications that link to this page (online services). We are committed to handling personal information in strict compliance with the specific provisions of applicable privacy laws worldwide. The Tap It Systems Privacy Policy was updated on April 1, 2015. 

## Web Site Privacy Policies

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Tap it Systems collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from you ("User") of the www.tapitsystems.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Tap it Systems. This privacy statement is designed to provide information about the privacy and data collection practices for the site: https://www.tapitsystems.com. The Site is operated by Tap It Systems.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our site coordinator at tony@tapitsystems.com or by postal mail to:

  * Tap It Systems
  * P.O. Box 23965
  * Phoenix, AZ USA
  * 85063

Tapitsystems.com collects information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. 

#### Identifying Information

In general, you may visit the Site without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself. In some areas of the Site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to process an order, offer services that require registration, assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you. Generally, Tap It Systems may use information collected by you in one of the following ways: 

  * Register on any of our web sites;
  * To process transactions;
  * Provide feedback to an online survey or tell us about an idea or suggestion;
  * Participate in a rebate program, contest, or other promotional offer;
  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs); 
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you);
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs); 
  * Request information or files from technical support or customer service.

In these instances, Tap It Systems will ask for your name, address, e-mail address, phone number and other appropriate information needed to provide you with these services. In all instances, if you receive a newsletter or other mailing from us, you will always be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, traded, loaned, leased, subleased, redistributed, posted, broadcasted, modified, transmitted or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

#### Tap It Systems Protects Your Information

Tap It Systems implements a variety of security measures to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

#### Sharing Information With Third Parties

Tap It Systems will not sell, share, rent, exchange, transfer, trade, loan, lease, sublease, redistribute, post, broadcast, modify, transmit, or otherwise give to any other company or person(s), for any reason, your personal information without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. We also do not sell or rent your personal information to non-affiliated third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We store and process your personal information on computers located in the United States that are protected by technological as well as physical security devices. You can access and modify the information you provide us and choose not to receive certain communications by modifying your preferences. We retain information provided by users at the time of registration, and all information regarding transactions on the Site. If you object to your personal information being used as described above, please do not register or use our services. 

#### Online Store

Tap It Systems online store is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your identifying information. If you choose, you may set up an account. This will allow you to have a customized order page for express ordering and to view your purchasing history. To protect your privacy, we have designed the Sites to include certain steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections in an account. You will always have access to this account information and can view it, update it or correct it at any time. To access your information, you will need to use a password. 

When purchasing products through the our web site, the order form will also ask you to provide a daytime telephone number. However, the telephone number is only used to quickly resolve questions relative to an order, such as to clarify customer email addresses that are inactive, or entered incorrectly.

#### Cookies and Other Technologies

At times, we will use a feature on your web browser to send your computer a "cookie". We do not use cookies to retrieve any personal information from your computer. Tap It Systems website(s), online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our websites people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy. Tap It Systems may use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website, online services, and applications. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with Tap It Systems more convenient and personal. For example, knowing your first name lets us welcome you the next time you visit the Tap It Systems website. Knowing your country and language, helps us provide a customized and more useful shopping experience. Knowing someone using your computer or device has shopped for a certain product or used a particular service helps us make our advertising and email communications more relevant to your interests. And knowing your contact information, hardware identifiers, and information about your computer or device helps us personalize your operating system, and provide you with better customer service. Please note that certain features of the Tap It Systems website will not be available once cookies are disabled. If you choose to disable cookies, please be aware some, or all, functions of the Site(s) may not function properly.

#### Children's Privacy Protection

Tap It Systems is sensitive to the heightened need to protect the privacy of children under the age of 13. ALL products and material on Tap It Systems website(s) are not intended for children, and are not targeted to children, or anyone under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect data from children and, if we learn that we have received personal data from a child, we will immediately take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account. Anyone who uses Tap It Systems website(s) services MUST be 18 years of age or older. By using our website services, you agree to the Terms and Conditions of Use, and Our Privacy Policies, you warrant and represent to us that you are 18 years of age or older. You, (Buyer), acknowledges and understands you must be 18 years of age to purchase long guns, and 21 years of age to purchase handguns.

#### Law and Harm

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Tap It Systems rights or property. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third parties, including a governments, request to disclose your information.

#### Changes to this Policy

Tap It Systems may from time to time revise its privacy policy. You should therefore periodically visit this page, so you are aware of any such revisions. We will not, however, use your existing information in a manner not previously disclosed. You will be advised and have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information.   
Contacting Us. If you have any questions about our privacy policy and/or the practices of our web site, you can write to:

  * Tap It Systems
  * P.O. Box 23965
  * Phoenix, AZ USA
  * 85063
